ntta.org 2013-05-01

# Privacy Policy

**_Our Commitment to Privacy_**

The NTTA has created this security and privacy statement in order to document and communicate its commitment to doing business with the highest ethical standards and appropriate internal controls.

We respect the privacy of your information. We provide this explanation about our online information practices as a show of our commitment to protect your privacy.

 ** _The Information We Collect_**

You may browse our website without providing any information whatsoever. Our website's TollTag application form and business opportunities registration requires users to give us contact information. This information is used to provide information to those who inquire about accounts, services, and to bid on business opportunities. This information is also used to get in touch with customers when necessary. From time to time, the information gathered through this site will be used to notify you about services and opportunities that we think will be of interest to you.

We may share the information we collect about you with third parties from the following categories: collection agencies, government agencies, credit card companies, check processing companies, banks, and our interoperability partners and their licensees.

In addition, we automatically gather general statistical information about our Website and visitors. We use this data in the aggregate to determine how much our customers use parts of our site so we can improve our site. We may provide this statistical information to third parties, but when we do so we do not provide personally-identifying information without your permission.

Some features of our site may be available only through the use of a cookie. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Generally, we use cookies to remind us who you are and enable continued access to your account information so you do not have to re-enter it. Preference and options configurations in your browser determine if and how a cookie will be accepted. You can change those configurations on your computer if you desire. By changing your preferences, you can accept all cookies, you can be notified when a cookie is set, or you can reject all cookies. If you do so and cookies are disabled, you may be required to re-enter your information more often and certain features of our site may be unavailable.

**_The Way We Use Information_**

Our site does not covertly capture information regarding the specific activities of any particular user. We do not have any arrangements with any other sites to track or monitor user activities on the Web. Our site does, however, produce reports that permit us to view your activity on our site in anonymous or aggregated form. We do not use cookies, web bugs, or any other active content mechanism to capture or maintain information about users without their prior consent. The only personal information that we capture has been specifically submitted to us through the request-for-more-information form. We do not store any persistent information on your computer.

We may also use or disclose information to resolve disputes, investigate problems, or enforce our User Agreement. At times, we may review status or activity of multiple users to do so. We may disclose or access information whenever we believe in good faith that the law so requires or if we otherwise consider it necessary to do so to maintain service and improve our products and services.

**_Security_**

We employ reasonable and current security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information.

Your account information and profile are password-protected. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. Remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished your session. This is to help ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place where others may have access to it.

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secure. As a result, while we try to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

**_How You Can Update or Correct Your Information_**

You can access the information that we collect online and maintain through normal updating methods. Use www.ntta.org to update or correct this information. Your account can be deactivated by contacting customer service at 972-818-NTTA (6882). By deactivating your TollTag account, you may not continue to use the NTTA Express Lanes but attended or cash-only lanes are available for your use.

During the normal course of doing business, we will continue to share your information among our business units and third parties as necessary in order to service your accounts with us.

**_Precautions For Children_**

The NTTA does not attempt to collect personal information from children. If a child sends personal information to us, and this information can be identified as originating from a child, the information will be deleted. We cannot always determine which information originates with a user that is a child. We do not maintain databases about children.

 ** _Information Usage_**

When you disclose personal information to us, that is where it stays. The only exception involves disclosure according to normal business practice, for instance for the collection of tolls, and according to the orders of a court, for example responding to a subpoena or search warrant. We do not sell, rent, trade, lend, or otherwise transfer such personal information to affiliates, subsidiaries, sister companies, holding companies, parent companies, strategic partners, or any other organization.

**_Links to Other Sites_**

This site contains a number of links to other sites. The NTTA is not responsible for the security or privacy practices of these sites, the products or services offered by these sites, or the content appearing at these sites. The NTTA does not endorse any of the products or services marketed at these other sites.

**_Security Measures_**

This site is protected with a variety of security measures such as change control procedures, passwords, and physical access controls. We also employ a variety of other mechanisms to ensure that data you provide is not lost, misused, or altered inappropriately. These controls include data confidentiality policies and regular database backups.

**_Contacting Us_**

With respect to this web site, there are two options regarding your personal information. If you wish to contact us about our services or business opportunities, then you need to disclose your contact information so that we can service your request, or if you do not wish to contact us about our products or services, we will have gathered no information about you, and you do not need to take further action. If you have elected to pursue the first of these options, after you have obtained the information you sought, you may at any time tell us to remove your name and other contact information from our database.

If you wish to remove your name and related information from our database, we will promptly take action to comply with your request. We are pleased to process address error correction notices and address change requests through any of the following channels:

  * Sending regular mail to PO Box 260729, Plano, TX 75026
  * Calling 972-818-NTTA (6882) during regular business hours

If you have any questions about this security and privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with our company, you can contact us using any of the above communications channels.

 ** _Changes to Our Policy_**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of February 23, 2006. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be communicated through our website at least 48 hours in advance of its effective date. Information collected before changes are made will be secured according to the previous Privacy Policy.

_**Your Consent**_

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information in the manner we describe.
